<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Timelines on louis&#39;s portfolio</title>
        <link>https://louiscklaw.github.io/timeline/</link>
        <description>Recent content in Timelines on louis&#39;s portfolio</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://louiscklaw.github.io/timeline/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        
        <item>
            <title>Handy/Hi. inc.</title>
            <link>https://louiscklaw.github.io/timeline/handyhiinc/</link>
            <pubDate>Wed, 07 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            
            <guid>https://louiscklaw.github.io/timeline/handyhiinc/</guid>
            <description>PRODUCTS  handy, the innovative flagship product from Tink Labs Limited, is a new benchmark for travel technology. When implemented as an in-room solution through hotel partners, handy combines the functionality of a personal smartphone and hotel in-room phone services into one fully integrated device. Each handy smartphone is customized for the hotel property and provides guests with unlimited internet, local and international calls, as well as an interactive city guide and one-click access to the hotel&amp;rsquo;s concierge and amenities.</description>
            <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h2 id="products">PRODUCTS</h2>
<blockquote>
<p>handy, the innovative flagship product from Tink Labs Limited, is a new benchmark for travel technology. When implemented as an in-room solution through hotel partners, handy combines the functionality of a personal smartphone and hotel in-room phone services into one fully integrated device. Each handy smartphone is customized for the hotel property and provides guests with unlimited internet, local and international calls, as well as an interactive city guide and one-click access to the hotel&rsquo;s concierge and amenities.
The development of handy is the first step towards achieving Tink Labs&rsquo; goal of addressing the needs of the global traveler. handy, a proven service in Hong Kong and Singapore has had unanimously positive reviews from both hotel partners and guests. It is now available also in London, Paris, Istanbul, Bangkok, Macau and Dubai, and is currently undergoing global expansion to the world&rsquo;s top travel destinations.</p>
</blockquote>
]]></content>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Sierrawireless</title>
            <link>https://louiscklaw.github.io/timeline/sierrawireless/</link>
            <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            
            <guid>https://louiscklaw.github.io/timeline/sierrawireless/</guid>
            <description>Description/Job Summary  We have an opportunity for a Software Test Engineer, Co-op to join our Module Integration team in Richmond. In this role, you will gain experience in wireless data communication modems, wireless network data communication protocols, development of software test automation scripts, software test methodology &amp;amp; techniques, and commercial software development life cycle.
 Responsibilities  Execute manual and automated tests for various products Develop manual and automated tests Analyze requirements and develop comprehensive test cases Analyze defects, create clear bug reports, and verify bug fixes Assist and collaborate closely with development team and other teams to troubleshoot technical issues Communicate well, track testing progress and write accurate test reports Assist in mentoring and training new co-op students Required Education, Experience &amp;amp; Competencies Strong written and oral communication skills Experience in writing test plans and complex test cases Software test development, programming, or scripting experience Knowledge of data communication, networking and protocols Ability to work effectively both independently and within a team environment Desired Education, Experience &amp;amp; Competencies Knowledge of Linux operating system and Linux command line usage is an asset  About sierra wireless    </description>
            <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h3 id="descriptionjob-summary">Description/Job Summary</h3>
<blockquote>
<p>We have an opportunity for a Software Test Engineer, Co-op to join our Module Integration team in Richmond. In this role, you will gain experience in wireless data communication modems, wireless network data communication protocols, development of software test automation scripts, software test methodology &amp; techniques, and commercial software development life cycle.</p>
</blockquote>
<h3 id="responsibilities">Responsibilities</h3>
<ul>
<li>Execute manual and automated tests for various products</li>
<li>Develop manual and automated tests</li>
<li>Analyze requirements and develop comprehensive test cases</li>
<li>Analyze defects, create clear bug reports, and verify bug fixes</li>
<li>Assist and collaborate closely with development team and other teams to troubleshoot technical issues</li>
<li>Communicate well, track testing progress and write accurate test reports</li>
<li>Assist in mentoring and training new co-op students</li>
<li>Required Education, Experience &amp; Competencies</li>
<li>Strong written and oral communication skills</li>
<li>Experience in writing test plans and complex test cases</li>
<li>Software test development, programming, or scripting experience</li>
<li>Knowledge of data communication, networking and protocols</li>
<li>Ability to work effectively both independently and within a team environment</li>
<li>Desired Education, Experience &amp; Competencies</li>
<li>Knowledge of Linux operating system and Linux command line usage is an asset</li>
</ul>
<a href="About%20sierra%20wireless" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">About sierra wireless
  <svg style="width:16px; height: 16px;padding-top: 2px;" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" width="24" height="24" viewBox="0 0 24 24" fill="none" stroke="currentColor" stroke-width="2" stroke-linecap="round" stroke-linejoin="round" class="feather feather-globe"><circle cx="12" cy="12" r="10"></circle><line x1="2" y1="12" x2="22" y2="12"></line><path d="M12 2a15.3 15.3 0 0 1 4 10 15.3 15.3 0 0 1-4 10 15.3 15.3 0 0 1-4-10 15.3 15.3 0 0 1 4-10z"></path></svg>


  <svg style="width:16px; height: 16px;padding-top: 2px;" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" width="24" height="24" viewBox="0 0 24 24" fill="none" stroke="currentColor" stroke-width="2" stroke-linecap="round" stroke-linejoin="round" class="feather feather-arrow-up-right"><line x1="7" y1="17" x2="17" y2="7"></line><polyline points="7 7 17 7 17 17"></polyline></svg>
</a>

]]></content>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>china mobile hong kong</title>
            <link>https://louiscklaw.github.io/timeline/chinamobilehongkong/</link>
            <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
            
            <guid>https://louiscklaw.github.io/timeline/chinamobilehongkong/</guid>
            <description>Description  Perform site hunting for suitable cell site to meet coverage and capacity requirement Perform indoor and outdoor radio system design Provide document for site configuration Conduct antenna reconfiguration of existing sites Perform coverage simulation with the use of RF planning tool Perform fine tuning of the repeater and amplifier to optimize the coverage and minimize the interference Perform uplink interference troubleshooting Evaluate new antenna, combiner and radio equipment To be successful in this position, you should meet the following requirements:  About CMHK    </description>
            <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h3 id="description">Description</h3>
<ul>
<li>Perform site hunting for suitable cell site to meet coverage and capacity requirement</li>
<li>Perform indoor and outdoor radio system design</li>
<li>Provide document for site configuration</li>
<li>Conduct antenna reconfiguration of existing sites</li>
<li>Perform coverage simulation with the use of RF planning tool</li>
<li>Perform fine tuning of the repeater and amplifier to optimize the coverage and minimize the interference</li>
<li>Perform uplink interference troubleshooting</li>
<li>Evaluate new antenna, combiner and radio equipment</li>
<li>To be successful in this position, you should meet the following requirements:</li>
</ul>
<a href="About%20CMHK" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">About CMHK
  <svg style="width:16px; height: 16px;padding-top: 2px;" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" width="24" height="24" viewBox="0 0 24 24" fill="none" stroke="currentColor" stroke-width="2" stroke-linecap="round" stroke-linejoin="round" class="feather feather-globe"><circle cx="12" cy="12" r="10"></circle><line x1="2" y1="12" x2="22" y2="12"></line><path d="M12 2a15.3 15.3 0 0 1 4 10 15.3 15.3 0 0 1-4 10 15.3 15.3 0 0 1-4-10 15.3 15.3 0 0 1 4-10z"></path></svg>


  <svg style="width:16px; height: 16px;padding-top: 2px;" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" width="24" height="24" viewBox="0 0 24 24" fill="none" stroke="currentColor" stroke-width="2" stroke-linecap="round" stroke-linejoin="round" class="feather feather-arrow-up-right"><line x1="7" y1="17" x2="17" y2="7"></line><polyline points="7 7 17 7 17 17"></polyline></svg>
</a>

]]></content>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
